<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>lynnmrtzvi &#8211; Lynn</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 15:27:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Deutsch; my eternal struggle</title>
		<link>./../../../2024/11/16/deutsch-my-eternal-struggle/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2024/11/16/deutsch-my-eternal-struggle/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[lynnmrtzvi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 15:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hobby]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[languages]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It was almost 3 years ago that I decided I wanted to learn German.With the enthusiasm I had for languages, I've ordered my German Textbooks and started learning right away.One month, two months... one year and then death.I realized I no longer wanted to learn the language. Nothing could make me want to learn it, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<pre class="wp-block-verse">It was almost 3 years ago that I decided I wanted to learn German.<br>With the enthusiasm I had for languages, I've ordered my German Textbooks and started learning right away.<br>One month, two months... one year and then <strong>death</strong>.<br>I realized I no longer wanted to learn the language. Nothing could make me want to learn it, so I stopped but the expectation was still there so I studied new stuff on and off, without caring to review the old ones.<br>There were a lot of factors that contributed to me stop learning German such as; perfectionism, lack of plan and priority, lack of resource management, being on my own and most importantly: <strong>PROCRASTINATION</strong>.<br>If you go online, you'll find people who claim they achieved fluency in German (or any other language) in a short period of time.<br>Regardless of who's telling the truth and who lies, I really believe in the Parkinson law which says the course of action<br>stretches depending on the time you put into it.<br>So the more time you put into it, you're most likely to get it done faster and giving German which is a very complex<br>language grammar-wise, you are to put a lot of concentrated time into it in order to even be able to form a simple sentence.<br></pre>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">where am I and what I wanna do?</h3>



<pre class="wp-block-verse">In terms of level, I'm still very much a beginner in the vast field of the German language.<br>Since the last method (textbook) didn't really work for me, I modified my approach and got two other books. One is <strong>Assimil</strong> and the other is called <strong>Begegnungen</strong>.<br>Assimil is consisted of 100 short lessons. All lessons are in form of short dialogs presented in both German and English and you are to learn German through English.<br>These lessons are fun, they also have native audio files and can be done in less than an hour.<br>I'm in my second phase lesson 52 now. <br>It is said that after completing all 100 lesson both passive and active phases, you'll be somewhere around B2.<br>I am planning to use Assimil as my main resource and supplement it with Begegnungen which is a more structured textbook but the difference is that Begegnungen is designed for both classroom and self-studying that's why I find it way more convenient that any other textbooks. Also I'll be reading and listening more to German on a daily basis and cultivate using German in my life.<br>I am really excited about the results after finishing these books.</pre>



<p><em>All my results will be posted so stay tuned </em>:))</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2024/11/16/deutsch-my-eternal-struggle/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One little honest note</title>
		<link>./../../../2024/11/16/82/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2024/11/16/82/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[lynnmrtzvi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 13:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[book]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=82</guid>

					<description><![CDATA["Humans can love.And as beautiful that is, it scares me. I'm scared to face the fact that the way I feel is not special to me.Doesn't it sound stupid sometimes how we try to be special in anything?I wonder if it's the going overboard that makes me stand out or the other way around; being [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<pre class="wp-block-verse">"Humans can love.<br>And as beautiful that is, it scares me. <br>I'm scared to face the fact that the way I feel is not special to me.<br>Doesn't it sound stupid sometimes how we try to be special in anything?<br>I wonder if it's the going overboard that makes me stand out or the other way around; being indifferent.<br><br>When and where do we find the love which we don't have to change ourselves for?<br>It's exhausting to be around people who don't see through me."<br></pre>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2024/11/16/82/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life is unforeseen</title>
		<link>./../../../2024/11/16/life-is-unforeseen/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2024/11/16/life-is-unforeseen/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[lynnmrtzvi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 12:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[book]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poetry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=79</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Life is unforeseenLike the brand new smile of a passer byOr like a meal you made yourself carelesslyBut ended up enjoying it.Like the letters you got from your classmatesOr like the isolation that came with being differentLike the biggest dream that once felt like airBut now that you have it you're still not thereLike the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<pre class="wp-block-verse"><em><br>Life is unforeseen<br>Like the brand new smile of a passer by<br>Or like a meal you made yourself carelessly<br>But ended up enjoying it.<br>Like the letters you got from your classmates<br>Or like the isolation that came with being different<br>Like the biggest dream that once felt like air<br>But now that you have it you're still not there<br>Like the cries of a newborn<br>Or like the fresh tears<br>That are being shed for the dead<br>And all the time you're wondering<br>Where you could be instead,<br>But let the day soak<br>And let the pain settle<br>Cause what you'll hunt for tomorrow<br>Is neither good or bad<br>And nor right or wrong<br>But it's unforeseen</em>.</pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2024/11/16/life-is-unforeseen/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Re-starting is exhausting!</title>
		<link>./../../../2024/11/16/re-starting-is-exhausting/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2024/11/16/re-starting-is-exhausting/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[lynnmrtzvi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 08:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=42</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Yesterday I saw this somewhere written; &#8220;Most people start working and get consistent not because of motivation, but because they are afraid to start over.&#8221; To think about it, I know that feeling. For me fear and exhaustion are the two reasons that keep me working even when I feel unmotivated." I don't wanna gain [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Yesterday I saw this somewhere written;</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p class="has-primary-color has-text-color has-link-color wp-elements-643786ee15a6d2559bc0efeeef723d2e"> &#8220;Most people start working and get consistent not because of motivation, but because they are afraid to start over.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>



<pre class="wp-block-verse">To think about it, I know that feeling. For me fear and exhaustion are the two reasons that keep me working even when I feel unmotivated.<br>" I don't wanna gain back the weight again, I don't wanna just be re-learning Em on guitar. I don't wanna be learning basic words and phrases again."</pre>



<p>I guess what I am trying to say is that working and staying consistent is really difficult but what&#8217;s even more exhausting, it&#8217;s starting over, again and again and again just because you felt like you can&#8217;t do it all those times before.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s the matter of facing yourself and being aware of your abilities and also what you need and what you wanna be and learning how to balance all of those in a way that benefits you.</p>



<p>Are you exhausted of starting again, too?</p>



<p>Then let&#8217;s learn to stay consistent, together.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2024/11/16/re-starting-is-exhausting/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
